# VISHAL WAKHARE

Sr. Digital Marketing Trainer | Consultant

Email-id: - vishrw@gmail.com

Mob. No: - 9762574607

Linkedin:- https://www.linkedin.com/in/vishalwakhare/

#### **Professional Profile**

Sr. Digital Marketing Trainer | Consultant with 2+ years of experience in Google Ads, Social Media tools and technologies, with a track record of creating and implementing successful campaigns. Worked closely with clients to develop and execute a proactive, budget management, social content calendar, managing all phases of digital marketing initiatives from concept through delivery and optimization.

#### **List Of Tools:-**

- **SEO and SEM**: Google Adwords, WordPress, Google Analytics, Google Search Console, Microsoft ads, Ubersuggest, Google trends, Buffer, Canva, Mailchimp.
- Social media channels: Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram, Pinterest, YouTube, Reddit and Tumblr.

#### **Skills**

- Strategy Making as per clients requirement.
- Suggesting creative ideas and strategy for campaign design and management.
- Google Adwords.
- Google Tag Manager
- Social Media Marketing
- Social Media Optimization
- PPC Management
- Campaign Budget Management
- Search Engine Optimization (on page and off page)
- Email Marketing
- Lead Generation
- Google Analytics
- Google Search Console
- Keyword Planner, Google Trends and Uber suggest
- Social Media Conversations
- Event Campaign Management

### **Work Experience**

## 1) Pashium Institute of Digital Marketing (Jan 2019 to present)

Designation: Sr. Digital Marketing Trainer | Consultant

- Provide in-class training on Digital Marketing.
- Helping learners in the practical execution of the digital concept.
- Delivering trial sessions to students.
- Handling day-to-day Search Engine Marketing (SEM) and Social Media Marketing (SMM) activities including campaign planning implementation and performance review.
- Monitoring the success of Social Media Campaigns through media analytics and dashboards.
- Creating engaging social media strategies and execution plans that cultivated audiences increased web presence and enhanced brand awareness.
- Reporting of campaigns with in-depth analysis on performance of keywords, bounce rates, etc.

### 2) <u>Digitize Brand Hub India Pvt. Ltd. (Jan 2018 To Jan 2019)</u>

Designation: Digital Marketing Trainer

- Provide in-class training on Digital Marketing.
- Helping learners in the practical execution of the digital concept.
- Handling day-to-day Search Engine Marketing (SEM) and Social Media Marketing (SMM) activities including campaign planning implementation and performance review.
- Monitoring the success of Social Media Campaigns through media analytics and dashboards.
- Creating engaging social media strategies and execution plans that cultivated audiences increased web presence and enhanced brand awareness.
- Reporting of campaigns with in-depth analysis on performance of keywords, bounce rates, etc.

## 3) Digitize Brand Hub (India) Pvt. Ltd. (July 2017- Jan 2018)

Designation: Intern

- Work with Digital Marketing Manager to refine social media strategy and best practices
- Assist in managing social media channels (Facebook, Twitter, Instagram)
- Keep up to date and informed on new social media trends and adapt accordingly
- Ensure proper messaging is being executed online
- Identify leaders and influencers (internal/external) and engage them in brand activities

### **Educational Qualification**

- Bachelor Of Engineering in Mechanical From Kj Educational Institute with 73.6 %
- HSC passed from CBSE BOARD with 61.4%
- SSC passed from CBSE BOARD with 8.0 CGPA

#### **Certifications**

- Google Tag Manager
- Advanced Google Adwords Training
- Completed Practical Digital Marketing course from Digital Trainee in 2017, Pune
- Internal Quality Auditor ISO 9001:2008
- Internal Quality Auditor ISO 16949
- Six-Sigma Green Belt-Lean

### **Extra-Curricular Activities**

- Conducted Staff Training at Ties Group Of Institute on Digital Marketing.
- Delivered Workshop to more than 50+ Dentists across Pune, Mumbai And Nashik.

### **Clients**

- Surya Housing
- Ties Group Of Institute
- Excel Plus
- Siddha Buildtech
- Amplus Filing
- Dental Arena
- le festiva
- Pashium Web Solutions

### **Declaration**

I hereby declare that the information mentioned above is correct to the best of my knowledge and I bear full responsibility of the authenticity of the particulars mentioned above.

Date:

Place: Pune Mr.Vishal R. Wakhare